OK, as you can see we've down loaded the image we want to create for our transfer.
I got this in a Microsoft Office picture manager.
And I've scaled it to the sized that I believe that I want, so I get the best resolution as far as the pixels are concern.
Once I have in the Microsoft Office picture manager, I'll come over here to the flip horizontal because I want this picture to be mirrored so it turns out backwards as I print it out.
Once it's backwards when it's printed out that makes me know that it will actually look like this on t-shirt.
So, hit the hit the flip horizontal button.
As you can see it's now in a mirror type of form.
I'll simply click on the image, copy the image, and then I'll go into my Microsoft Word and just simply paste the image into the document itself.
Now I could do a print preview to make sure that the image is the size that I want.
If it's not, I'll close out of this and then I could use the image editor or the image editing box and just simply increase it to the size that I want, that I want the image to be.
Once I got it to the size that I'm looking for, then I will just simply go to the to the print preview making sure that it's the size that I want.
And then just go up here and click my print button so that I can print it out.
Making sure that I'm actually printing this out on a test piece of paper, which is just a regular blank piece of paper rather than wasting a transfer paper.
Now we've got our transfer on a on a blank piece of paper and I'm ready to print this out on my transfer paper because I like the way this is looking so far.
So, I'll print this out on my transfer paper.
I'll look my transfer paper making sure that the green line is facing me.
So, as this goes through the type of printer that I'm using it will actually print on the blank side of the transfer paper.
My transfer paper is loaded up and I'll just hit print again.
And now we have the transfer that we want on our transfer paper.
And notice the green line is on the back.
I can see the transfer through the transfer paper.
So, this allows me a good idea of what this transfer will look like on the t-shirt itself.
But all of the ink is on this side.
We want to make sure that we don't touch the ink on the transfer just yet as soon as it's printed out because the ink will tend to smudge a little bit and we don't want to create that on our t-shirt.
So now we're ready to put this on our t-shirt.
We'll just to do a few little things like trimming the excess out and we'll be ready to apply this.